hrsmart.com 2012-12-23

# Privacy Policy | Human Resource Software | Applicant Tracking System

**ASP PRIVACY POLICY**

 _Effective March 1, 2006_

This statement discloses HRsmart, Inc.'s ("HRsmart's") privacy policy with respect to the personally identifiable information ("personal information") it may maintain while operating as an application service provider ("ASP") for its clients. Any information HRsmart collects by other means, such as through the website www.hrsmart.com or off-line, is subject to a different policy and practice.

This privacy policy applies only to the personal information HRsmart maintains in its capacity as an ASP. HRsmart builds custom software applications to help clients manage their human resources information. HRsmart's clients use this software to store, manipulate and extract human resources data. Typically, clients input data to the application's database. HRsmart's clients also may permit other parties to input data, such as vendors and job applicants. Our clients, not HRsmart, control which parties may enter data to the database. Similarly, our clients, not HRsmart, control which parties, such as employees and vendors, may access the data stored in the database. If you have a question about how a particular client protects personal information, we encourage you to review its privacy policy.

HRsmart complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. HRsmart has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view HRsmart’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

**1\. Notice**  
HRsmart does not collect personal information. Clients use our applications to store and manage data that often contains personal information. Individuals should consult our clients' privacy policies for information about how their personal information may be collected and used by our clients.

**2\. Choice**  
HRsmart will maintain personal information in accordance with this privacy policy. If at any point we change our policy, we will post a notice on this webpage to advise the public of such revisions. HRsmart does not have the ability to provide individuals with a choice regarding to whom our clients may disclose individuals' personal information or whether it is used for a purpose that is compatible with the purpose for which it was originally collected. We recommend that individuals consult our clients' privacy policies if they have questions about how these companies may collect, retain, use or share personal information.

**3\. Onward Transfer**  
We do not share any personal information with third parties. Our clients control the transfer, if any, of personal information to third parties. 

**4\. Security**  
HRsmart strives to protect the personal information it maintains on behalf of its clients. We have implemented physical and technological safeguards to help protect against the loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction of personal information. 

**5\. Data Integrity**  
HRsmart will not use the personal information it maintains in any manner. You should consult our clients' privacy policies for information about how they may use or process personal information.

**6\. Access**  
We maintain personal information on behalf of our clients. We provide our clients with the technological capacity to grant and limit access to personal information in accordance with their business and privacy practices. To correct, amend or delete inaccurate personal information, you should contact the company to which you provided this information.

**7\. Enforcement**  
HRsmart has verified that it complies with this privacy policy. If you have any questions or complaints about this policy, please contact at [marketing@hrsmart.com](mailto:marketing@hrsmart.com) or mail at 2929 N. Central Expressway, Suite 110, Richardson, TX 75080. If we are unable to resolve your complaint, you may contact the appropriate Data Protection Authority in the European Union.

 **[HRsmart Privacy Document  
](http://web.ita.doc.gov/safeharbor/SHList.nsf/f6cff20f4d3b8a3185256966006f7cde/e9cacdd23a053a3e85257125005f66ca?OpenDocument&Highlight=2,hrsmart)**
